moonit.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Moonit LLC ("Moonit," "we" or "our company") has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy which governs our flagship Website Moonit.com. We realize the importance of feeling safe online and want you to feel comfortable using our personalized services and exchanging information on Moonit.com. We are committed to protecting your personal information and will take reasonable steps to see that this privacy policy is followed within our company. The statement below outlines the privacy practices solely for the Website located at www.Moonit.com and not for any other product or service. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and subject to, the terms and conditions of our Terms of Service. All capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meaning set forth in the Terms of Service.

I.INFORMATION COLLECTED  
In order to provide you with personalized services and features, we ask you to register and establish your personal profile. During the registration process we will ask you for information such as your name, gender, birth-related information, e-mail address, password and, in certain cases, geographic location. This information is used to calculate an accurate natal chart and provide you with the best possible personalized services over time. Your e-mail address, together with a password, is used to secure your profile and to make our personalized e-mail services available to you.  
We collect many different types of non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities on our site through your IP address or most-recently-visited URL. However, we do not collect any personally identifiable information directly from you unless you voluntarily submit such information to us, by using our products and services or by filling out a form or short survey through our progressive profiling process or unless you authorize us to automatically collect such information from you. In order to access the Services through the Application, you must authorize Moonit to collect information about your location to make full use of the Application’s functionality.  
Personally identifiable information is primarily collected to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the part of the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as name, gender, e-mail address, birth date, birth location and time of birth (to the extent available). Customers who personalize our service come back regularly, so we do everything we can to make Moonit.com your service and give you just the content you wish to receive.

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Moonit does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Services is directed to persons under 13. If Moonit learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected through the Services without verified parental consent, then Moonit will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

II.USE OF INFORMATION  
The personally identifiable information voluntarily provided by you is used and shared as described in this policy, including to:  
1\. provide you with the services or products you have requested from us;  
2\. send you promotional offers for various products and services via email;  
3\. permit our vendors and contractors to access your information, but they are only allowed to use such personal information in connection with the services they provide for the Website; or  
4\. enable you to post and transmit information about yourself at your discretion.  
5\. allow you to purchase premium services by agreeing to authorize our third party provider Stripe to accept your secure credit card and debit card payments; you can reference their Privacy provisions here: https://stripe.com/us/privacy.

We may also obtain information about you from third parties and use that information to enhance the information that we already have about you. For instance, if we just have your name and email address, we may use a third party to obtain your telephone number and physical address. All of the combined information will be used in accordance with this policy.  
Please note that we reserve the right to access and/or disclose personal information and non-personal information we gather as required by courts or administrative agencies and to the extent required to permit us to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, our Website's Terms of Service, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper. We may also disclose and/or transfer your personal information in connection with a sale, merger or reorganization of all or a part of Moonit. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.  
Non-personally identifiable information about you may be shared by us with any number of third parties, and those third parties may use that information for our benefit or for their own benefit. However, such information will not specifically identify you.

III.ONLINE COMMUNICATIONS IN PUBLIC FORUMS  
You should be aware that personally identifiable information which you voluntarily include and transmit online in a posting, comment, public profile or other public forum may be viewed and used by others. We are unable to control such uses of your personally identifiable information, and by using such services you assume the risk that the personally identifiable information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties. You also assume the risk that you might be exposed to objectionable content and conduct by using public forums such as these. You agree not to hold Moonit responsible for the content or actions of other users of the Website.

IV.USE OF COOKIES  
When you view our Website or advertisements, we or our advertisers or other parties might store or collect some information on or from your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file, such as a web beacon or clear gif. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive to facilitate your current and future visits to our site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, save passwords so you won't have to enter it each time you visit the site, and for other purposes. You can set your Web browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept the cookie. You can also deactivate cookies by clicking on the Sign Out link on the Moonit.com Home page. However, some parts of the Moonit.com Website may not work properly if you deactivate or reject cookies.

V.SECURITY  
We have implemented and follow commercially reasonable industry standard technical and procedural measures to protect against unauthorized access and use of your personal information. However, you should know that neither we nor any other Website can fully eliminate these risks. For more information on protecting your privacy online, please visit www.ftc.gov/privacy. In the unlikely event that an unauthorized third party compromises Moonit’s security measures, Moonit will not be responsible for any damages directly or indirectly caused by an unauthorized third party’s ability to view, use or disseminate such information. 

VI.OTHER WEB SITE LINKS  
Moonit.com contains links to other Websites. Moonit is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other Websites.

VII.CORRECT/UPDATE OR OPT-OUT  
You can change the personal information you previously provided by editing your profile in your Account Details. If you wish to delete your iPhone app account, simply enter “Delete” into the Feedback section of the application. Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases, so if your information has been shared as permitted by this policy, we will not be able to remove such information from the records of a third party. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from our records.  
If you have chosen to receive information and alerts by e-mail, you can at any time cancel this by clicking on the link "You are receiving MoonMail" on your personalized Home Page and selecting the option "Unsubscribe."

VIII.DELETE PROFILE  
You can delete your profile at any time by clicking on the "delete profile" link.

IX.CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY  
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use personally identifiable information in a way that materially differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes.

X.UNITED STATES OF AMERICA  
Our Website is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Website, which is governed by United States law, you freely and specifically give us your consent to export your personally identifiable information to the USA and to store and use it in the USA as specified in this policy.

XI.CONTACTING US  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at privacy@moonit.com.

XII.EFFECTIVE DATE  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 1, 2013.
